Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009.
Mus. Arc. 24
Buffalo Musicians' Association (Buffalo, N.Y.)
37 boxes 50 bound volumes 1 official stamp
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library 112 Baird Hall Buffalo, New York 14260-4750 United States Phone: 716 645-2924 Fax: 716 645-3906
Buffalo Musicians' Association records dating from 1889 to the present. Bulk of collection includes meeting minutes and financial records. Collection contains materials from Local 43 (white musicians' union), Local 533 (black musicians' union), Local 92 (merger of Locals 43 and 533, still in existence), Local 649 (Hamburg, N.Y., merged with Local 92 in 1999), and general AFM records.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Buffalo Musicians' Union, 2003.
Accruals and Additions
Further accruals are expected on a regular basis.
Historical Note
In 1886, the National League of Musicians (NLM) was founded and had over 100 locals within ten years. One of these was Local 23 of Buffalo. A few years later, the American Federation of Labor (AFL) began organizing locals with the view of musicians as workers, contrary to the NLM view of musicians as artists. By 1896, members of the NLM grew dissatisfied and formed the American Federation of Musicians (AFM), which was, and still is, chartered by the AFL. In the very early days of the AFM, Buffalo's Local 23 began to discuss joining the AFM and then consequently became AFM Local 43. The NLM dissolved over the first few years of the 1900s.
As was customary for many AFM locals in the country, there were two racially segregated locals in Buffalo. The Buffalo Colored Musicians' Union, Local 533 was founded in 1917. It existed as a separate entity from Local 43, although logistical complications arose as more bands became racially integrated. In the 1960s, it was clear that a merger of the two locals would make business much more practical. In 1964, AFM President Herbert Kenin mandated that all racially segregated AFM locals merge. Difficulties arose, however, in getting Locals 43 and 533 to reach a merger agreement. Local 533 was particularly reluctant because this meant being absorbed into a union nine times their size, possibly losing their real estate, losing their elected officers, and having all their funds absorbed into the large account of the merged local's money. These were valid concerns, as many other black AFM locals had faced these setbacks in their mergers. The Civil Rights Act of 1965 ruled that there could be no segregated union locals, but this did not require the locals to merge. It simply meant that a person of any race could join either local. In fact, Local 533 had two white members after this. By the end of 1967, Local 533 drew up a merger agreement with the help of AFM officials. The members of Local 533 voted for it, but then Local 43 voted against it. In the fall of 1968, after having warned the locals on multiple occasions, AFM President Kenin finally stepped in and mandated a non-negotiable Plan of Merger. The new merged local would be designated Local 92, and the Plan's stipulations were a reasonably fair compromise. While Local 533 members were somewhat unhappy about the loss of their local, and while integration was not entirely smooth, the merger ultimately worked out in the long run. Local 92 is still a diverse and active organization.
This collection also contains some records from Local 649, which was the Hamburg Musicians' Association. This local was absorbed into Local 92 in 1999, as many considered it inconvenient to have such a fragmentation of locals in Western New York.
Background information found in the following sources:
Loft, Abram. "Unions, musicians'" in The New Grove Dictionary of American Music. London: Macmillan, 1986.
McRae, Richard Kenneth. Musicians' Association Local 533 of the American Federation of Musicians, and its Role in the Development of Black Music in Buffalo, New York. Buffalo, N.Y., 1993.
Scope and Content Note
The Buffalo Musicians' Association Records contain materials dating from 1889, from the days when it was Local 23 of the National League of Musicians. This local continued on as Local 43 of the American Federation of Musicians. The collection also contains records dating from 1923 from the Buffalo Colored Musicians Union, Local 533. When these two locals merged in 1969, they became Local 92, which still exists today. The collection contains Local 92's records up to the present. The collection also contains some records of Local 649, Hamburg, NY (which merged with Local 92 in 1999), as well as some general AFM material. The collection's materials are in the form of meeting minutes, financial records, correspondence, wage scales, directories, constitutions, by-laws, news clippings, attendance records, as well as the official stamp of Local 43.
Arrangement
The label "item" has been used to sequentially number this collection. It may indicate either a single bound volume or a folder with multiple leaves. The collection is arranged in three series, with subseries as indicated:
I. Local 43
A. Board Meeting Minutes
B. Record Books: Meeting Attendance
C. Member Directory
D. Financial Books
E. Directory and Wage Scale Books
F. Official Stamp
G. Correspondence
II. Local 533
A. General Meeting Minutes
B. Board Meeting Minutes
C. Correspondence
D. News Clippings
E. Directory and Wage Scale Books
F. Attendance Records
III. Local 92
A. Meeting Minutes
B. Correspondence
C. Receipts
D. Directory and Wage Scale Books
E. Directory and Instrumentation Books
F. Constitution and By-Laws
G. Price Lists
H. Directory, Instrumentation, Constitution, By-Laws, and Price List
IV. Local 649
V. American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada
A. Constitution and By-Laws
Container List
- Local 43 Records, 1889-1968, I.; 49 bound volumes, 23 boxes, 1 official stamp
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1889-1968, I.A; 9 bound volumes, 20 boxes
    - 1889-1890, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 1)
    - 1890-1896, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 2)
    - 1896-1900, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 3)
    - 1900-1908, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 4)
    - 1900-1904, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 5)
    - 1905-1908, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 6)
    - 1908-1910, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 7)
    - 1909-1914, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 8)
    - 1927, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 9)
    - Special Meeting, September 26, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 10)
    - Board Meeting, October 1, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 12)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 13)
    - General Meeting, October 14, 1927, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 14)
    - Board Meeting, October 19, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 15)
    - Board Meeting, October 25, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 16)
    - Board Meeting, November 1, 1927, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 17)
    - Board Meeting, November 8, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 18)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 19)
    - Board Meeting, November 11, 1927, 3 leaves (Box 1, Item 20)
    - General Meeting, November 11, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 21)
    - Board Meeting, November 18, 1927, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 22)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 23)
    - General Meeting, November 25, 1927, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 24)
    - Board Meeting, November 28, 1927, 4 leaves (Box 1, Item 25)
    - Board Meeting, December 1, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 26)
    - Board Meeting, December 19, 1927, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 27)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 28)
    - Board Meeting, December 30, 1927, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 29)
    - Board Meeting, January 6, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 30)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 31)
    - General Meeting, January 13, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 32)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 33)
    - Board Meeting, January 31, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 34)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1928, 5 leaves (Box 1, Item 35)
    - Board Meeting, February 10, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 36)
    - Board Meeting, February 29, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 37)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 38)
    - Special Meeting, March 16, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 39)
    - Board Meeting, March 17, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 40)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 41)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 42)
    - General Meeting, April 13, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 43)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 44)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 45)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 46)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 47)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 48)
    - Board Meeting, June 15, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 49)
    - Board Meeting, June 22, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 50)
    - Board Meeting June 26, 1928, 3 leaves (Box 1, Item 51)
    - Board Meeting, June 29, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 52)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 53)
    - General Meeting, July 13, 1928, 6 leaves (Box 1, Item 54)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 55)
    - Board Meeting, July 27, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 56)
    - Board Meeting, August 1, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 57)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 58)
    - Board Meeting, August 24, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 59)
    - Board Meeting, August 31, 1928, 3 leaves (Box 1, Item 60)
    - General Meeting, September 7, 1928, 4 leaves (Box 1, Item 61)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 62)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 63)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 64)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 65)
    - Board Meeting, November 2, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 66)
    - General Meeting, November 2, 1928, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 67)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 68)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 69)
    - Board Meeting, November 23, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 70)
    - Board Meeting, November 30, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 71)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 72)
    - Board Meeting, December 21, 1928, 1 leaves (Box 1, Item 73)
    - Board Meeting, December 28, 1928, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 74)
    - Board Meeting, January 4, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 75)
    - General Meeting, January 4, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 76)
    - Board Meeting, January 7, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 77)
    - Board Meeting, January 15, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 78)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 79)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 80)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 81)
    - Board Meeting, February 14, 1929, 3 leaves (Box 1, Item 82)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 83)
    - Board Meeting, March 18, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 84)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 85)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 86)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 87)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 88)
    - General Meeting, May 3, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 89)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 90)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 91)
    - Board Meeting, June 14, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 92)
    - Board Meeting, June 18, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 93)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 94)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 95)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 96)
    - General Meeting, July 5, 1929, 1 leaves (Box 1, Item 97)
    - Board Meeting, July 9, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 98)
    - Board Meeting, July 17, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 99)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 100)
    - Board Meeting, August 6, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 101)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 102)
    - Board Meeting, August 23, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 103)
    - Board Meeting, September 3, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 104)
    - General Meeting, September 6, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 105)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 106)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 107)
    - Special General Meeting, September 27, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 108)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 109)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 110)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 111)
    - Board Meeting, October 25, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 112)
    - General Meeting, November 1, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 113)
    - Board Meeting, November 8, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 114)
    - Board Meeting, November 15, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 115)
    - Board Meeting, November 29, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 116)
    - Board Meeting, December 13, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 117)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 118)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 119)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 120)
    - General Meeting, January 3, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 1, Item 121)
    - Board Meeting, January 7, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 122)
    - Board Meeting, January 14, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 123)
    - Board Meeting, January 21, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 124)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 125)
    - Board Meeting, February 14, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 126)
    - Board Meeting, March 4, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 127)
    - Board Meeting, March 11, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 128)
    - General Meeting, March 14, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 129)
    - Board Meeting, March 25, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 130)
    - Board Meeting, April 8, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 131)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 132)
    - Board Meeting, May 6, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 133)
    - General Meeting, May 9, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 134)
    - Board Meeting, May 27, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 135)
    - Board Meeting, June 3, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 136)
    - Board Meeting, June 24, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 137)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 138)
    - Board Meeting, July 1, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 139)
    - Board Meeting, July 2, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 140)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 141)
    - General Meeting, July 11, 1930, 3 leaves (Box 2, Item 142)
    - Board Meeting, July 22, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 143)
    - Board Meeting, July 29, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 144)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 145)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 146)
    - Board Meeting, August 19, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 147)
    - Board Meeting, August 26, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 148)
    - Board Meeting, September 9, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 149)
    - General Meeting, September 12, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 150)
    - Board Meeting, September 15, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 151)
    - Board Meeting, September 19, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 152)
    - Board Meeting, September 25, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 153)
    - Board Meeting, September 30, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 154)
    - Board Meeting, October 16, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 155)
    - Board Meeting, October 24, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 156)
    - Board Meeting, October 28, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 157)
    - Board Meeting, October 31, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 158)
    - Board Meeting, November 4, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 159)
    - General Meeting, November 14, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 160)
    - Board Meeting, November 28, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 161)
    - Board Meeting, December 16, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 162)
    - Board Meeting, December 16, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 163)
    - Board Meeting, December 31, 1930, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 164)
    - Board Meeting, January 20, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 165)
    - General Meeting, January 21, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 166)
    - Board Meeting, January 30, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 167)
    - Board Meeting, February 10, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 168)
    - Board Meeting, February 24, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 169)
    - Board Meeting, March 17, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 170)
    - Board Meeting, March 24, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 171)
    - Board Meeting, April 14, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 172)
    - General Meeting, April 15, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 173)
    - Board Meeting, April 28, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 174)
    - Board Meeting, May 5, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 175)
    - Board Meeting, May 26, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 176)
    - Board Meeting, June 23, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 177)
    - Board Meeting, June 30, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 178)
    - Board Meeting, July 7, 1931, 8 leaves (Box 2, Item 179)
    - General Meeting, July 15, 1931, 3 leaves (Box 2, Item 180)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 181)
    - Board Meeting, August 4, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 182)
    - Board Meeting, August 11, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 183)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 184)
    - Board Meeting, August 25, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 185)
    - Special General Meeting, August 30, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 186)
    - Board Meeting, August 31, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 187)
    - Board Meeting, September 2, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 188)
    - Board Meeting, September 8, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 189)
    - Board Meeting, September 17, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 190)
    - Special General Meeting, September 27, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 191)
    - Board Meeting, September 29, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 192)
    - Board Meeting, October 1, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 193)
    - Special General Meeting, October 18, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 194)
    - General Meeting, October 21, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 195)
    - Special General Meeting, October 25, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 196)
    - Board Meeting, October 27, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 197)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 198)
    - Board Meeting, December 1, 1931, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 199)
    - Board Meeting, December 15, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 200)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1931, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 201)
    - Board Meeting, January 20, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 202)
    - General Meeting, January 20, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 203)
    - Board Meeting, January 26, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 204)
    - Board Meeting, January 28, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 205)
    - Board Meeting, February 2, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 206)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 207)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 208)
    - Board Meeting, March 17, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 209)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 210)
    - Board Meeting, March 31, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 211)
    - Special General Meeting, March 31, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 212)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 213)
    - Board Meeting, April 14, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 214)
    - General Meeting, April 20, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 215)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 216)
    - Special General Meeting, May 4, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 217)
    - Board Meeting, May 5, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 218)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 219)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 220)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 221)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 222)
    - Board Meeting, June 2, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 223)
    - Board Meeting, June 13, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 224)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 225)
    - General Meeting, July 20, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 226)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 227)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 228)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 229)
    - Special General Meeting, August 23, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 230)
    - Special General Meeting, August 30, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 231)
    - Board Meeting, August 31, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 232)
    - Special General Meeting, September 10, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 233)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 234)
    - Board Meeting, September 22, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 235)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 236)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 237)
    - General Meeting, October 19, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 238)
    - General Meeting, October 27, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 239)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 240)
    - Board Meeting, November 23, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 241)
    - Board Meeting, December 8, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 242)
    - Board Meeting, December 17, 1932, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 243)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1932, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 244)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 245)
    - General Meeting, January 4, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 246)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 247)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 248)
    - Special General Meeting, January 20, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 249)
    - General Meeting, February 1, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 250)
    - Board Meeting, February 6, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 251)
    - Adjourned General Meeting, February 9, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 252)
    - Special General Meeting, February 11, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 253)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1933, 3 leaves (Box 2, Item 254)
    - General Meeting, March 1, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 255)
    - Board Meeting, March 9, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 256)
    - Board Meeting, March 16, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 1, Item 257)
    - Special General Meeting, March 21, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 258)
    - Board Meeting, March 23, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 259)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 260)
    - General Meeting, April 5, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 261)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 262)
    - Board Meeting, April 27, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 263)
    - General Meeting, May 3, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 264)
    - Board Meeting, May 4, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 265)
    - Board Meeting, May 25, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 266)
    - Board Meeting, June 7, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 267)
    - General Meeting, June 7, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 268)
    - Board Meeting, June 15, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 269)
    - Board Meeting, June 27, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 270)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 271)
    - General Meeting, July 5, 1933, 2 leaves (Box 2, Item 272)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 2, Item 273)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 274)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 275)
    - Special General Meeting, July 24, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 276)
    - Board Meeting, July 31, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 277)